Catholic Charities USA
The American Catholic Research Center and University Archives
- Series 3: General Administration Files, 1920-2008; (101 Boxes)
  - Subseries 3.5: Religious Organizations, 1960-1985; (8 Boxes)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Lilly Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Lilly-Raskob, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Lilly-Raskob, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Luce, Henry-Foundation, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: General, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: General (1), 1977 (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: General (2), 1977 (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: General, 1978-1979 (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: Funding Committee Meeting, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: Funding Committee Meeting, January, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: Funding Committee Meeting, April, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: Funding Committee Meeting, September, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: Funding Committee Meeting, January, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 36)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: Funding Committee Meeting, June, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 37)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Marianist Sharing Fund: Funding Committee Meeting, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 38)
    - Jerome Ernst and Parish Social Ministry: Robinson, Peter, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - Subseries 3.6: Secular Organizations, 1961-1984; (13 Boxes)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (1), 1967 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (2), 1967 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (1), 1968 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (2), 1968 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (1), 1969 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (2), 1969 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (1), 1970 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (2), 1970 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (3), 1970 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General (4), 1970 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General, 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): General, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meetings, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meetings, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, February, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, April, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, June, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, August, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, October, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, February, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, June, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, February, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 27)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, October, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 28)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, April, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 29)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, November, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 30)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Meeting, May, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 31)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 32)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Board of Directors Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 33)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): By-Laws, Personnel Practices, Staff Organization Chart, 1970-1972 (Box 98, Folder 34)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Correspondence re Position of Executive Director, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 35)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee (1), 1970 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee (2), 1970 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee (3), 1970 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee (1), 1971 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee (2), 1971 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Financial Reports, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Financial Reports, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Job Corps, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Personnel, 1967-1969 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Personnel Policies, 1980-1982 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS): Restructuring, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - National Association of Social Workers: General, 1962-1963 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - National Association of Social Workers: General, 1964-1966 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - National Association of Social Workers: General, 1966-1967 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - National Association of Social Workers: General, 1967-1968 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - National Association of Social Workers: General, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (1), 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (2), 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (3), 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (4), 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (5), 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (1), 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (2), 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (3), 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (4), 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 30)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (5), 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (6), 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 32)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (7), 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 33)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion (8), 1971-1975 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion: Current Materials, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion Policy, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Abortion Proposal-Ad Hoc Committee, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Academy of Certified Social Workers: Separation, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Anderson, Joseph, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Bulletin, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - National Association of Social Workers: By Laws and Resolutions, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Chapter and Coalition Efforts to Oppose Policy, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Chapter Delegates to the NASW Assembly, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Church's Stand on Other Life Issues, 1973-1975 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Connecticut Consumers Against Abortion (1), ca. 1975 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Connecticut Consumers Against Abortion (2), ca. 1975 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Correspondence Re: Memos, Policy (1), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Correspondence Re: Memos, Policy (2), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Current Concerns of Members, ca. 1975 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly Report, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly: General (1), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly: General (2), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly: Policy Statements (1), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly: Policy Statements (2), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly: Policy Statements (3), 1975 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Delegate Assembly, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Gerwe, Sr. Barbara, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Information Re: Items for Delegate Assembly, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Local Efforts to Approve NASW Abortion Policy, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: List by State, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Names Arriving After May 16, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 29)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Policy, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 30)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Proposals, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 31)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Returning Questionnaire, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: "Supportive of our Position,", 1975 (Box 100, Folder 33)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Alabama-Minnesota List of Members, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Alabama-Minnesota List of Members Not Supportive of Policy, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 35)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Missouri-Wyoming List of Members, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 36)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Missouri-Wyoming List of Members Not Supportive of Policy, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 37)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Membership: Typed Lists, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 38)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Memo from Councilors of Religious Committees, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Memos, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Moral Implications of Abortion Policy, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - National Association of Social Workers: National Alliance for Family Life, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - National Association of Social Workers: National Association of Christians in Social Life, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - National Association of Social Workers: National Commission for Social Work Careers, 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Official List of Delegates to NASW Dinner, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Other Contacts Re: Abortion Policy, ca. 1975 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Position Statement Paper (1), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      Abortion
    - National Association of Social Workers: Position Statement Paper (2), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Position Statement Paper (3), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Position Statement Paper (4), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Preliminary Schedule for Delegate Assembly, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Project Strategy, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Proposals from Previous Delegate Assemblies, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Publicity, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Regional Convenors, ca. 1975 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Resource Persons Active in 1967 and 1971 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Rights of the Unborn, Committee-New York City, ca. 1975 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Score Cards for Delegate Votes, ca. 1975 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Social Workers Concerned for NASW (1), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Social Workers Concerned for NASW (2), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Social Workers Concerned for NASW (3), 1975 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Social Workers Concerned for NASW, 1975-1976 (Box 101, Folder 24)
      Diocesan Coordinators
    - National Association of Social Workers: Social Workers Concerned for NASW, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Society for Clinical Social Work, ca. 1975 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Sponsoring Committee, ca. 1975 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - National Association of Social Workers: State Licensing and Regulation of Social Workers, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Steering Committee, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Steering Committee (1), 1975-1976 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Steering Committee (2), 1975-1976 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Substitute Proposals: Abortion, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - National Association of Social Workers: Washington, D.C. Chapter, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General, 1969-1970 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General, 1970-1972 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General (1), 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General (2), 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General, 1975-1976 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General (1), 1978 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General (2), 1978 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): General, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Board of Directors, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Board of Directors, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Board of Directors, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Board of Directors, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Board of Directors (1), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Board of Directors (2), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Executive Committee (1), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Executive Committee (2), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Executive Committee, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Federal Interagency Coordinating, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Finance Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Nominating Committee, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 20)
      Board of Directors
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Steering Committee for Cooperating Organizations Group, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action (NCVA): Subcommittee on ACTION, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): General, 1961-1962 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): General, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): General, 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): General, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 26)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): General, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Advisory Council on Public Assistance, 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Annual Reports, 1962-1967 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Committee on Field Service, 1963-1966 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Committee on Personnel, 1964-1967 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Contributions of NCCC, 1961-1967 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Greenleigh Study, 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): NCCC Representation, 1961-1965 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): NCCC Representation, 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Reports and Publications, 1961-1967 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Survey of Employment Experience in Selected Voluntary Health and Welfare (1), 1961 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Survey of Employment Experience in Selected Voluntary Health and Welfare (2), 1961 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly (NSWA): Uniform Accounting Project, 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): General, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): General, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): General, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): General, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Annual Report, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Annual Report, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Board of Directors, 1968-1969 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Board of Directors, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Board of Directors, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Board of Directors, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Board Meeting, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): By-Laws, 1969-1970 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): ByLaws, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Committee on Personnel, 1968-1973 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Conference of Executives (1), 1967-1972 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Conference of Executives (2), 1967-1972 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Conference on International Social Development, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Confidentiality, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Council for Social Planning and Program Development, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Executive Committee, 1971, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Executives of National Voluntary Agencies, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Federal Encouragement of Voluntary Action, 1969 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Forum on Drug Abuse, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Forum on Social Issues and Policies, 1969-1971 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): International Social Development Committee, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Joint Committee (on Merging), 1971 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Memo to Members, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (NASPD): National Health Council, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 11)